A Guide to the Frank Lebby Stanton Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #8470-a
Frank Lebby Stanton Collection 1895-1904
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
8470-a
16 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Purchase [ 1967 Oct 4 ] 1968 Jan 25
Item Listing
- Letters
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, 1895 Jan 5; ALS, 1 p.
    [Encloses poem, "
    A Song of Gifts
    "; complains about theft of his poem, "
    How Shall I Love You
    , " which he published in
    Ladies Home Journal
    and which later appeared in
    Jenness Miller Magazine
    under the signature of " Will C. Ferril. "]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, 1896 Jul 7; ALS, 2 p.
    [Congratulates him on honors bestowed in England; encloses poem, "
    The Love Lights of Home
    "; suggests alternate titles.]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, 1896 Jul 23; ALS, 3 p.
    [States poem, "
    Lights of Home
    , " rejected by Bok, was accepted by Mrs. Sangster for
    Harper's Bazaar
    submits another piece; hopes Bok will occasionally like his work; affirms his friendship; mentions John Wesley,
    Chicago Times-Herald
    , and
    . ]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, 1896 Jul 28; ALS, 1 p.
    [Sends a piece; hopes Bok will like it.]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to [ Edward W. Bok], n. d.; ALS, 2 p.
    [Discusses article about John Wesley, especially his stay in Georgia; mentions Rev. W. J. Scott. ]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, 1896 Oct 26; ALS, 2 p.
    [Promises to send "When John Wesley preached in Georgia" article, complete with pictures; thinks picture of Wesley Oaks most important; includes marginal note by [Bok] reimbursing Stanton for expenses related to article illustrations.]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, 1898 Feb 8; TLS, 1 p.
    [Accepts suggestions; sends two revised copies.]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, 1898 Mar 22; TLS, 1 p.
    [Submits poems, "
    Only to Love You
    , " "
    His Refuge
    , " and "
    The Love-Sign of the Rose
    "; hopes "
    " will interest, written in dialect of old black nurses.]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, 1898 Oct 14; TLS, 1 p.
    [Says he is willing to have one of his poems set to music but leaves the decision to Bok; says he is glad to entertain the Boks in Atlanta. ]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, 1904 Feb 23; ALS, 2 p.
    [Discusses writing lyrics for a tune suggested by Bok; says he may try to adapt one of five love songs.]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, 1904 Apr 9; ALS, 1 p.
    [Encloses included clipping, "Dishonesty as a Source of Mirth."]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, n. d.; ALS, 1 p.
    [Expresses gratitude for complimentary letter; says he is busy with newspaper work; promises to save his best work for Bok in the future; encloses bits of verse.]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, n. d.; ALS, 1 p.
    [Discusses article in progress; says he is pleased that Bok liked "
    Love's Kingdom
    . "]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, n. d.; ALS, 1 p.
    [Submits poem, "
    The Comforter
    "; says he will forgive Bok if he returns a piece again.]
  - Frank Lebby Stanton to Edward W. Bok, n. d.; TLS, 1 p.
    In the Old Fields
- Photograph
  - Magazine Photograph of Frank Lebby Stanton, head and shoulders, Photo